Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 71, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 50: Supplment A: Factory Job Classifications and Rate Ranges, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 51: Master Organization Chart, 1969; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 52: New Graduate Hiring Rates, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 53: Performance Review Instruction Sheet, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 54: Financial Assistance to Education, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 55: Regulations and Guide for Employee Participation, 1960; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Employee Educational Assistance Program
- Box: 71, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Set of Specifications, 1957; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Comparison of Principal Benefits for New York Telephone Company Employees (Upstate), Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: New York Central System Passenger Service, 1957; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Specifications: Proposed Health Insurance Plan for New York State Employees, 1957; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Author: Alexander A. Falk, President
- Box: 71, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Safety Trade Group 462, 1954; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Lifeline: A Line to Save A Life, 1967; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 1 - No. 1
  - Item 3: Lifeline - A Line to Save A Life, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 10 - No. 4
  - Item 4: Lifeline - A Line to Save A Life: Greater New York Safety Council, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 10 - No. 3
  - Item 5: Electrical Employers Self Insurance Safety Plan, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Notes: A Five-Year Report
- Box: 71, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Management Organisation, 1950; Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Box: 71, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employment Application for Professional, Administrative and Specialized Positions, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Description of Secretarial Training, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Description of Secretarial Training, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Schedule of Insurance, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Executive Development Activism in Johnson & Johnson and Affiliated Companies, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Suggestions for Carrying on Our Upward Communications, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Development and growth of Johnson & Johnson Training Program, 1950; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Industrial Relations Section, 1951; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Executive Audit, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Executive Audit, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: What Do You Suggest?, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Final Report of Upgruard Communications Project, 1951; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Upward Communications: A Project in Executive Development Using The Syndicate Method, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Notes: Final Report
  - Item 14: Management Development Program for the Manufacturing Division, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Use of Role Playing for Supervisory Development, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Author: William V. Machaver
  - Item 16: Teaching Aids, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Training Department Activities, 1954, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Explanation of the Group Accident Insurance Program for Employees and Wives, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Counseling Executives After Merit Rating or Evaluation, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Conference Leadership Training, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Research & Development, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: A Survey of Needs and Methods in Executive Development Emphasizing The Method of Directed Guidance, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Author: Earl G. Planty, Carlos A. Efferson
  - Item 23: Our Credo, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Box: 71, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Agreement to our Pittsburgh Factory Contract, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Author: P.R. Greene
  - Item 2: Suggestion System, 1948; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Requisition for Personnel, 1949; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: H.J. Heinz Company General Vacations Policy, Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Salaried Job Description, 1951; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: N.J. Heinz Company General Vacations Policy, Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Management Chart, 1957; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Safety News, 1950; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Management Organization Chart, Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Company Organization Chart, Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Medina Factory, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Salaried Job Description: Manager Personnel, 1951; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Personnel Division Home Office, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Management Organization Chart, 1975; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Management Organization Chart, 1970; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Wage Rates, 1955; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Box: 71, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Suggestions For Counseling After Merit Rating or Evaluation, 1950; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: November 21, 1950
  - Item 2: 78 Years of Progress; A History Of Johnson & Johnson, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Executive Development, 1950; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Author: Earl G. Planty
    Notes: November 2, 1950
  - Item 4: A Program For The Develoment Of Executives And Supervisors, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Author: William V. Machaver, Training Director
    Notes: November, 1950
  - Item 5: Job Openings For Seniors And Graduate Students, Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: 1957-1958
  - Item 6: Selection Of Supervisory And Managerial Personnel, 1953; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Salaried Employees' Complaint Procedure, 1969; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1950; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Author: Charles Serraino; Simon Saller; Rudy Cammerata
  - Item 9: A Survey Of Needs And Methods In Executive Development Emphasizing The Method of Directed Guidance, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Author: Earl G. Planty; Carlos A. Efferson
    Notes: January and February, 1952
  - Item 10: Wage And Salary Administration Job Evaluation Method, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Johnson and Johnson Organizational Chart, 1954; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: February 1, 1953
  - Item 12: Management Development Program For The Manufacturing Divisor, 1954; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Personnel Department Report, 1950; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: 1949
  - Item 14: Employment Application For Professional, Administrative and Specialized Positions, 1954; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: General Education Program, 1955; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Testing Programs, 1958; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: The Johnson & Johnson Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: March 6
  - Item 18: Management Careers, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Your Retirement Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: January 1, 1966
  - Item 20: Research and Development at Johnson & Johnson, 1969; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: Hoover Report and Responsibilities of Citizenship, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: February 13, 1952
  - Item 22: Developing Leadership for To-morrow's Tasks, 1953; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: General Education Program, 1954; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: Conseling Executives After Merit Rating or Evaluation, Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Author: Earl G. Planty and Carlos E. Efferson
    Notes: A Project in Executive Development
- Box: 71, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: McGraw-Hill Inc., Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Employee Request for Group Insurance, Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Employee's Waiver of Group Insurance or Request for Discontinuance of Contributions, Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
    Notes: Exhibit "J- 2"
  - Item 4: Blue Cross - Blue Shield, Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
    Notes: Exhibit "K"
  - Item 5: Major Medical, Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
    Notes: Exhibit "K-2"
  - Item 6: McGraw-Hill Inc., Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
    Notes: Exhibit "K-3"
  - Item 7: Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: A Career for You With Standard & Poor's, Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Serving Man's Need for Knowledge, Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Pilot Program for Training Disadvantaged People, 1970; Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
    Notes: January-June, 1968
  - Item 11: Office Job Evaluation Program Procedure Manual, 1967; Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Box: 71, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Personnel Policies and Procedures Table of Contents, 1967; Publication (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Box: 71, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Office Traning Manual; Office Training Center - Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Office Traning Manual; Telephone Techniques, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Receptionist Duties, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Care of Your Typewriter, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Office Traning Manual; Typing Per Se (The Art of), Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Office Traning Manual; Sample of a Timed Writing, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Office Traning Manual; Proofreader Marks and Proofreader Exercises, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Office Traning Manual; Manuscript Typing, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Office Traning Manual; Tabular Typing, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Office Traning Manual; Rough Copy Typing - Rough Draft Typing, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Office Traning Manual; Duplicating Masters: Ditto - Stencil - Multilith - Xerox, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Office Traning Manual; Business English, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: Capitalization, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Use of Dictionary, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Word Division, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 16: Expressing Numbers, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Reference Books, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Vocabulary, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Spelling, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: Printing and Publishing Terms, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 21: McGraw-Hill Letter Set-up, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: McGraw-Hill Memorandum Set-up, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 23: Addressing Envelopes, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: Filing, Filing Procedures, and Indexing, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 25: Office Traning Manual, 1970; Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: Office Traning Manual; Location of McGraw-Hill Offices, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Box: 71, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Progress of Wages Under AFL Cannery Contract Since 1937, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Box: 71, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Little Mis'hap Speaks, 1954; Publication (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Your Job; Selling Personnel, Publication (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Executive Development Program, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Training Squad Program, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Training at Macy's, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 13)
- Box: 71, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: General Rules, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 14)
    Notes: June 1964
  - Item 2: Salary Policy, Publication (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Box: 71, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Salary Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 71, Folder 15)
    Notes: Revised July 1958
- Box: 71, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Profit - Sharing Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company; Interoffice Letter, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 16)
    Author: Frederick W. Oswald
    Notes: August 1, 1966
- Box: 71, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers Trust Company Executive Traning Program., Publication (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Box: 71, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Employment, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Employee Development and Training, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Change of Status, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Salary and Wage Administration, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Employee Rating, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Leave of Absence, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Vacations, Holidays, Overtime, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Employee Services, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
- Box: 71, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Industrial Compensation, Safety, Health, Publication (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Labor Relations, Publication (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Employee Relations Policy and Procedure Manual; Current Government Regulations, Publication (Box 71, Folder 19)
- Box: 71, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Mangement Control, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Flat Rate, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: F.E. Sales Development Program Tranee's Manual; Orientation, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
    Notes: Section 1
  - Item 4: F.E. Sales Development Program Tranee's Manual; Accounting, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
    Notes: Section 2
  - Item 5: POPular Sales Techniques; What People Want in a Product, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
    Notes: Section 2; Unit 1
  - Item 6: F.E. Sales Development Program Tranee's Manual; Parts, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
    Notes: Section 3
  - Item 7: POPular Sales Techniques, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
    Notes: Section 3, Unit 2
  - Item 8: F.E. Sales Development Program Tranee's Manual; Service, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
    Notes: Section 4
  - Item 9: Purpose of Manual, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Profit Analysis of Service Center, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
- Box: 71, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Machine Earnings, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Scheduling Work, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Job Ticket, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Parts Department, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Predelivery and Delivery Service, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Personnel, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Training, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Service Center Layout, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Library, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Warranty, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: Incentive Plans, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: Selling Service, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: POPular Sales Techniques; Sales Resistance, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
    Notes: Unit 3 Reference Manual
  - Item 14: F.E. Sales Development Program Trainee's Manual; New and Used Equipment, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
    Notes: Section 5
  - Item 15: POPular Sales Techniques; Closing the Sale, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
    Notes: Unit 4 Reference Manual
- Box: 72, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Guide for Office Supervisory Training, 1950; Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Box: 72, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor in Management, 1950; Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Notes: June 7, 1946
- Box: 72, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Plan of Action, 1951; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Box: 72, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Training Schedule for Relief Foremen, 1951; Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Box: 72, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Management's Right to Manage, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Author: Fred C. Edwards
    Notes: February, 1963
- Box: 72, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Amendatory Agreement, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Box: 72, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Human Relations in Supervision, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Box: 72, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Manufacturing Policy, 1954; Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Box: 72, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Manufacturing Policy, 1950; Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Box: 72, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Armstrong Educational Program for 1947, 1957; Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Agreement Between United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local No. 359 and Armstrong Cork Company, 1970; Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Notes: November 14, 1969
- Box: 72, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: General Personnel Department, 1950; Publication (Box 72, Folder 11)
    Notes: April 1, 1950
- Box: 72, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations Manual, 1950; Publication (Box 72, Folder 12)
    Notes: March 19, 1948
- Box: 72, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Relief Foremen Training Program Schedule, 1951; Publication (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Box: 72, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Economic Cooperation Administration Groups, 1951; Publication (Box 72, Folder 14)
    Notes: March 2, 1951
- Box: 72, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Organizational Chart, 1958; Publication (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Box: 72, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Organization Chart - Personnel Division, 1956; Publication (Box 72, Folder 16)
    Notes: Partial Organization October 1955
- Box: 72, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Employment Policy, 1950; Publication (Box 72, Folder 17)
- Box: 72, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Book Condensation of The Road Ahead, 1950; Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
    Notes: Statement to Employees
- Box: 72, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Your Hourly Rate, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Box: 72, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Armstrong Cork Company Careers, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Box: 72, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Equal Employment Opportunity, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
- Box: 72, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Record of Performance Under - Our Pledge to You, Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
- Box: 72, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Industrial Engineering at Armstrong, 1960; Publication (Box 72, Folder 23)
- Box: 72, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Suggestions for Progress, 1960; Publication (Box 72, Folder 24)
- Box: 72, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Armstrong, 1953; Publication (Box 72, Folder 25)
- Box: 72, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Industrial Engineering Manual, 1950; Publication (Box 72, Folder 26)
- Box: 72, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Personnel Objectives, 1953; Publication (Box 72, Folder 27)
- Box: 72, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Line and Staff Responsibilities and Relationships, 1954; Publication (Box 72, Folder 28)
    Author: C.J. Backstrand
    Notes: September 18, 1952
- Box: 72, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 29)
    Notes: March 1, 1966
- Box: 72, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Administrative Practice Course, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
    Notes: December 13-17, 1965
- Box: 72, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Armstrong Higher Education Gift Matching Program, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 31)
- Box: 72, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Hours of Work and Premium Compensation, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 32)
    Notes: Issued: June 15, 1961
- Box: 72, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Vacation Plan for Salaried Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 33)
    Notes: Issued: January 1, 1966
- Box: 72, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Wage Incentives, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 34)
    Notes: Issued: July 24, 1957
- Box: 72, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Manufacturing Policy; Wage Scales, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 35)
    Notes: Issued: June 15, 1954
- Box: 72, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Recruiting and Training of Sales Personnel in the Armstrong Cork Company, 1960; Publication (Box 72, Folder 36)
- Box: 72, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Manufacturing Policy, 1960; Publication (Box 72, Folder 37)
    Notes: Issued: May 2, 1960
- Box: 72, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 72, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Let's Look Ahead, 1959; Publication (Box 72, Folder 38)
    Author: Walter E. Hoadley, Jr.
    Notes: March 4, 1959
- Box: 72, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 72, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Objectives of Personnel Administration, 1957; Publication (Box 72, Folder 39)
- Box: 72, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 72, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Personnel Review, 1957; Publication (Box 72, Folder 40)
- Box: 72, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 72, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Master Mechanics Training, 1957; Publication (Box 72, Folder 41)
    Notes: January 16, 1957
- Box: 72, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 72, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Personnel Chart, 1953; Publication (Box 72, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: Personnel Chart, 1953; Publication (Box 72, Folder 42)
- Box: 72, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 72, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: General Personnel Department, 1953; Publication (Box 72, Folder 43)
- Box: 72, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 72, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Personnel Department, 1953; Publication (Box 72, Folder 44)
    Notes: September 1, 1950
- Box: 72, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 72, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Work Personnel and Labor Relations Department, 1953; Publication (Box 72, Folder 45)
- Box: 72, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 72, Folder 46)